✔ uploaded-file URLs are found anywhere in documents, with the documents that use them (720.0734ms)
✔ a backup stores the actual file bytes; a lost file is re-uploaded and every reference repointed (93.2641ms)
✔ a corrupted backup copy is refused instead of being re-uploaded (27.9062ms)
✔ starting class control starts the scheduled class happening now; joins become attendance; ending stores engagement and ends it (1821.1452ms)
✔ no class scheduled now → class control runs on its own; a class already live is reused but not ended by it (88.1662ms)
✔ another teacher's class is never linked (56.7528ms)
✔ owner customises branding, pages, subdomain, timezone and working days; the public sees only public parts (1467.3404ms)
✔ settings validation and permissions (57.6267ms)
✔ recording disabled by the institution: the teacher cannot switch it on or upload a recording (35.1374ms)
✔ consent required: students answer yes/no, the teacher sees the answers (57.7826ms)
✔ always_allowed: starting the class turns recording on with the consent rule (47.943ms)
✔ without an OpenAI key the teacher gets a clear message (903.4806ms)
✔ transcribe → subtitles attached to the lesson video → translated track → served as public VTT (135.6613ms)
✔ only the course teacher can generate, and only from the lesson's own media (no arbitrary URLs) (37.5163ms)
✔ VTT parse/build keeps timings and cue ids untouched (32.567ms)
✔ question bank: institution teachers share it; outsiders cannot see or use it (1465.6582ms)
✔ exams copy picked bank questions; a bank question from another institution is refused (72.2186ms)
✔ random subset + shuffled options per attempt; answers map back to the right question/option and grade on the attempt total (124.2164ms)
✔ integrity events: focus loss flags after the threshold, paste flags at once, other students cannot log on your attempt (66.8364ms)
✔ submitting from a different device than the attempt started on is logged and flagged (66.4454ms)
✔ resource search: students see published lessons of their courses with subject/grade/semester/teacher filters (1189.0785ms)
✔ course playlists reach that course's students only and cannot mix in other lessons (193.3162ms)
✔ students make private playlists; only the owner edits/deletes; reordering is saved (160.0799ms)
✔ equations, arrows, mind maps and images are stored on the shared board (945.9851ms)
✔ malformed rich items are rejected (25.8395ms)
ℹ tests 25
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 25
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 8447.1586
